by H.
Thank you for watching
ME
Know-It-All Grand Prix
me
To train your ability to adapt to unfamiliar topics, we have a round-table discussion on a favorite topic, but only one of the participants has no idea about the topic.
Can the "know-it-all" member, who has only studied the topic an hour in advance, answer the questions and get through the roundtable without being exposed?
The first topic of the night is Harry Potter!
The four members of the round-table discussion are as follows.
You four love Harry Potter, don't you?
Yes, I do.
It's scary, isn't it?
Okay, first question, Tamra.
If you could be a character in a film, what role would you play?
Oh, I don't know...
That's a tough one.
What do you mean?
Well, let's see...
I don't know... but I'm usually like this, so I get licked a lot.
That's why I admire the intelligent Ravenclaw.
Ravenclaw stars are pretty good.
I'm Hermione.
You already want to be in that position, don't you?
I really like Emma Watson.
I like her intelligence and bravery... and her relationship with Ron.
I thought she was going to get together with Harry, but she's going to Ron.
I know her so well.
I love Harry Potter.I love Harry Potter.
Hermione, including the romantic elements.
I see.
Yamashita-san becomes Hermione, and I want to be Ron.
What?
Why?
I want to kiss you.
Who? Yamashita told you?
He's a little clumsy, but I like his cute side.
Ron's good.
I like him because he's a little bit like me.
I like him.
I mean, the live-action version of the movie, Harry is cute when he's little, but...
But as he gets older, he becomes so much cooler.
I know. I know.
I totally understand.
Neville's the coolest.
I'm gonna put Neville on the chain.
No, no, no. I love Neville.
Come on, Ikeda.
I think I'll go with...
I'm going with Prisalyn.
Where do you want to be?
I want to be a teacher... and give Gryffindor 50 points off.
I see... I want to be a teacher.
I'd like to be a teacher.
You guys are pretty good at this.You're all relatively good.
Yes, they are.
Who's the know-it-all?
What's the next question?
What do you like?
She's much better than this.
That play's a lot of fun, too.
I'm an ambassador and I've seen it twice now, and it's amazing.
I've seen it twice now, and it's just amazing.
Okay, let's talk about your favorite scene.
I see... my favorite scene... but the first one, the Philosopher's Stone... it's the most striking.
And in the movie, they're all tiny, so it's cute how they interact with each other.
Even the most casual things are cute. Like the three of us sitting on the train, eating snacks.
Like beer and chocolate frogs. I kind of long to live in a dormitory.
I adore it. The way the three of them are so happy when they get a new dorm.
It's so cute. Like, "We're in the same dorm!
Like the relationship with Hermione... that's so cute.
I like the way Hermione and Ron are together, so when Ron drinks the poison, Hermione's next to him and she's watching over him and Ron says his name.
I'll never forget how excited she was when Ron said her name while she watched over him.
I know it's a little late in the game, but my favorite character is Cedric.
And when Cedric gets hit by the needle during the final defeat...
I was so moved by his bravery.
Well, that's it!
It's so hard!
It's so painful!
What in the world?
There's no one like the black-eyed man I saw earlier.Not a single one of them looks like the black eye you saw earlier.
I knew it was that easy to see.
Please do the magic you like best.
And for the last question, I'm going to ask you to do your favorite magic.
I like hairdressers with bingedium.
Ah~
Action.
Expecto Patrona.
Boomos.
Again, no big hint of scintillation here.
This concludes all the questions
Tamura's guess is
Yamashita-san.
Why Yamashita?
He's been talking about Ron and Yuu Hazama's love affair all day.
I thought maybe he looked it up an hour ago and learned it.
I see.
I'm Ikeda.
I haven't made many mistakes.
But one time when you told me about the stage...
Everyone except Ikeda just said yes, yes.
But only Ikeda looked at me like "Oh, really?
He looked at me like, "Is there going to be a stage?
I couldn't let my guard down.
I could feel their eyes on me.
Ikeda was on my radar the whole time.
Alien Prosean
I've never seen Paris Potter before.I've never seen Paris Potter.
Who are the know-it-all members?
Mr. Yamashita is going to be a comely I am Ron
Raise your hands, please.
Go ahead
Yes, sir.
You've done it!
That's great!
You're good.
I don't know any of them except Ron, Hermione and Hurley.
I said Hurley.
Hurley.
I have no idea.
Brilliant.
You were so good.
The next theme was the hit movie "Kimi no na wa.
Can Kagawa recognize any of these four members that he doesn't know at all?
Let's start with the first question.
Please share your favorite scene with the four of us.
Favorite scene
For now, I'll go with the stage style.
Let's get started. Let's get ready to go.
I can't choose all of them.
Can I say something first?
You know what?
Oh, my God!
I like it. I like it.
I love it.I like it.
You don't know my name.
I wrote it so you'd know my name.
I wrote it down.
Why do you like him?
I like you.
I like you so much, I can't understand a word anyone says.
I don't know.
Mitsuba said...
"I don't get it.
It's a little tight...
I can feel her hand squeezing mine.
I know... the part at the end where they pass each other and it's like...
The last scene.
Right there on the stairs.
But we've already passed each other once, right?
That's right.
On the train, look back.
Looking for him.
I love you guys.
It's great... it's great...
Oh, my God, they're working so well together.
It's super-plated.
Let's see if we can break it up with the next question so there's no tension.
What do you think your name is?
There's a clip in the back.
What do you think is the most iconic image of your name?
Or how many times it's been done.How many times already, and so on.
What is your name that the 4th place imagines
I'd like you to see what difference it makes in the picture.
I'd like everyone to see it.
Let's start here.
Here it is.
I'm a little bit bad at drawing, but...
But when I took over the house, when something happened, we exchanged letters in the diary.
When something happened at the new house, we exchanged messages in the diary, and it was very impressive.
I want to draw.
Then continue...
This is mine.
Yes, that's right.
Shinkai's film is really beautiful in the way he depicts the scenery.
The sky is so beautiful, as well as the city.
I love it so much that I drew this.
I see... you're right.
Yes, that's right.
This is another classic scene, but it's the scene where two people who love each other meet.
The meeting is before writing on the hand.
The most famous package.
You mean they meet there?
Yes, yes, yes.
Tamura.
It's a little confusing.
I've seen it before.
It's heavy.
That's why he's the guy with the rim.That's why he's the guy with that edge.
They're calling each other, but they can't see each other.
When they pass by each other and see each other, it's a great moment.
It gives you goosebumps.
It's also the best timing for the song to be played there.
This scene is famous, but it's so great!
The last question is, "Can Kanagawa recognize a familiar face?
Pose for your favorite scene.
Pause
Is this one by one or together?
All together
This is the most important first move, right here.
This is where you have to watch.
It's your favorite scene.
Three seconds to go.
321, please.
Ha-ha-ha.
Everyone's a little slow on the uptake.
Nice work.
I'll start with Tamura, but this time in reverse.
I know I mentioned this earlier, but...
At the end, when the two adults pass each other on the stairs...
"We've met before.
Mitsupu looks back like this
She's crying and looking at him like this.
It's so cute!
It's the face ofThis is the face of
This is the scene where the neck strap is pulled taut.
Toward the train.
Yes, yes, yes.
Now, Lilia...
I'm going to make sure that the two people who have been switched like this
Turn to the mirror and check.
She's saying something like "aikan".
I like the emo feeling at the end.
but I also like the slapstick at the beginning.
I like the way they switch places and look at each other's asses.
That's right.
I like Mie's brave scene where she stands up to her dad to evacuate the town.
Mie's brave scene when she confronts her father to evacuate the town.
I see.
There you go.
I get it.
I don't get it.
Now it's a little better.
I see.
Were there any signs of knowing among the four posers?
From all the questions, Kanagawa came up with...
Mayu Tamura.
Oh, yeah.
Why is that?
All of them are talking in the same scene.
I think there were a lot of hand touching and the last scene.
Because she's talking about the most common places.I thought maybe it was because I was talking about the main street.
I thought maybe you could see it.
I see.
No, I'm Lilia.
I wonder if that's not the same thing.
Tamura is starting to look suspicious.
Lilia seems the most vague in that sense.
I can hear you saying that.
It's true.
Who here has never seen "Your Name"?
Raise your hand.
Yes!
Yay!
I'm so glad.
You saw through that.
You didn't see it?
No.
Why not?
I was kind of late and then it was over.
And I didn't know when to look.
I didn't know.
You should watch it.
But I thought I'd watch it after reading everyone's stories and doing my own research.
I didn't see it... and now you're talking...
You're a genius!
It's pretty amazing, isn't it?
Next up is the national smash hit
Oni-no-Kiri no Tsurugi (Blade of the Demon)Blade of Demon's Destruction
This time, a more difficult version with multiple know-it-all members
Can Inoue spot all the know-it-alls?
It could be two, it could be three.
So there is a possibility that four people don't know about this at all.
There are four of them!
Then it looks like you don't even know the four hitters.
I don't know.
Who is the culprit behind the shocking statement?
Inoue, who himself is familiar with Onimete, asked the first question
Please describe your favorite character in one Kanji character.
Please describe your favorite character using only one kanji character.
The four of us were asked to choose one of the many Onimasu characters and describe him or her using what single kanji character.
Since you said it's okay, let's start with Ume
Janno
No, it's not.
You mean Ume likes men?
Actually, it's the Chinese character for man.
I see.
I'll go for that one.
I like Mr. Uzui.
He eats women.
I have three wives.
That's quite a license.
Yes, he's a character called "Pillar.
He's really cool.
Next is Yumiki!Now followed by Yumiki
Kanrodji
Sweet this is Mr. Kanroji
Uncle Kanro
Mr. Kanrodzie Uncle Karl
I got a bunch of curls today Please pick some up on your way home
I'm sorry, I don't know if this is related to the candy...
Mr. Kanrodzie! Mr. Kanrodzie, Mitsui!
I'm Zenichi.
I'm Zenichi and he's very cute and a bit silly.
He's cute and a bit silly, but I think that makes him a lovable character.
End of the show!
I support him.
I have a character named Tamayo-san.
She does things to support Sumijiro and his friends.
He's the one who collects demon's blood and makes medicine.
Yes, he's kind and I like him.
At this point, I think he's great.
There are at least two of you?
I don't even know them.
I understand a lot now.
I don't get it at all.
Oh, I see.
What's the jealousy in that?
Okay, so tell us what you know about the trivia.
After an hour of study, I'd like to see a little bit of the results.
Let's start with a trivia question. Who should we start with?
Let's start with who?E-Sakura-san
Okay, I'll start from the end.
I don't know any trivia about that.
I see.
Well, if you're just a casual fan, you might not know that.
Maybe.
I don't know anything.
You don't know?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
What's the other thing?
I've never watched anime in my life.
When Oni no Kai was popular, I didn't see it listed there.
I've recently started watching it a little while ago, so I haven't really gone into depth on the trivia.
I haven't gone as far as to look up the trivia in depth.
I see... I don't have any trivia.
Trivia
First of all...
How do you take my question?
I've worked with Mr. Shimono, the voice actor for Zen-itsu before.
So...
And we were having some kind of audition celebration.
When he was auditioning for Zen-itsu, he shouted a lot.
You know how Zenitsu always screams a lot?
He would say "wow" and "gah", so he had a lot of patterns for his screams.
They prepared many patterns of screams.
I made many patterns of screams.
I see.I see.
Sayyumikki...
I don't know if this is trivia.
in the manner of anxiety
Death of Daito
Daito no kisei
I can't understand it even though I'm hearing it clearly right now...
The death of the great...
"Great" is fine.
I don't need it.
It's "Dai".
Did you put "big" in "big"?
Just a big one.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's a big one.
Big!
I'm going.
"Death" is written as "river" and "river of death" is written as "river of deathless".
He's here!
He's a character.
He's here?
I was surprised when I first heard about it.
Is that trivia?
Well, you know...
Trivia is trivia.
Who in the world is the river that knows?
Who the hell knows?It's a river.
I'll call anyone who knows the river.
Can Inoue find them all in the last question?
If they make the next one, what do you think the story will be about?
No, no, no, it's hard.
No, no, no, no.
What do you mean next time?
Next time...
Well, Oni No Kai has already been finished... but you mean the next one, right?
Yes...
That's a tough one.
It's difficult.
It's more than knowledge.
Let's start from the back.
From the back.
What do you mean?
From Endo.
I've recently started watching that anime, but I don't know what it's about.
There's a lot of blood and grotesque images.
I thought there was a lot of blood and grotesque images, so I wanted to see something a little softer.
I wanted to see something softer.
I wanted to see something softer... more heartwarming.
I wanted to see something more heartwarming.
Yes, heartfelt.
Yes, I understand.
That's complicated.
Okay, Tsutsui.
I'd like to tell the story of the evil side, the demon side, from the perspective of the evil side's feelings.I'd like to tell the story of the evil side of the demon.
I'd like to see a story about the evil side, or a story about the evil side from the perspective of the feelings of the evil side.
I'd like to see something from that perspective.
Let's read and listen!
I'd like to see the world of the evil side too, just like Aya.
I wonder what they would say if something bad happened to them.
I'm sure there are unavoidable circumstances, and I'd like to see them explored more and more.
I swear to you that I want you to make the world a happy place for everyone.
Yes, sir.
Come on, Kumon.
I don't know what it is, but I'm one of them.
I really like that too.
But that's already been explained. Each character has his own story.
So, you beat Muzun, and Sumijiro almost became a demon, right?
I'd like to see a world where Sumijiro becomes a demon.
I also like to draw, so I'd like to see more characters.
I wonder if you were able to see through the love?
I've been trying to guess all of them, but I haven't been able to guess any of them.
How many of you have never heard of Onimete?
Inoue, who loves Onimete, arrived at the answer.
How many did you think?
Then, please announce them... Yumiki and Ayame.
Yumiki-san wrote "sweet" when writing a single kanji character, and I had an image of her going straight to the point.
Ayame-chan, in the last question, you wrote the story of the Oni side of the story.
Like this... like this...
I see.
There it is!
Nagatsuki's face.That face of Changzukuri.
Well, well, well.
It's written all over it.
I was just thinking...
Come on, Mr. Himura.
No, there's three of me.
There were a lot of them.
All but Ume.
I see.
There was a time when you didn't say anything.
You don't know anything about it.
Did she just say it out of the blue? I can't believe she didn't.
But I think Tsutsuri was already on board with that.
And the bad side.
I'm suspicious of Ume too, but...
When Ume was finishing her next project, she said it was too difficult.
There was a time when he was really upset.
I see.
So who is this deadbeat who's never seen or read Oni no Kensetsu no Kai?
Yay!
I knew it!
So there's no Don Pichon.
It's just like I said yesterday.
There are a lot of episodes on the demon side.
When you said there were a lot of episodes about demons...
I was surprised?
I thought, "Oh no!
I did it.I did it.
And you did a great job with the end, even though you didn't know about it.
No, I didn't know until about halfway through.
I'd never even seen the best one.
How dare you?
No, I didn't.
So I looked it up, but I wasn't interested in it, so I didn't get into it at all.
I didn't really know what breathing was either, so...
Anyway, I told Mai Tamura
I wanted to like Zenitsu first.
He's the one who wants to eat it.
Looks delicious!
It has strawberries in it.
Looks delicious.
How do you like it? It's crispy.
Crispy.
Mille-feuille.
Good soy sauce.
It's delicious.
Can I just say... am I allowed to eat this?
Can I eat soy sauce?
You can eat it.
I'm not supposed to eat it.
Asuka Saito's graduation concert
Blu-ray & DVD will be released!
I couldn't stop crying.
Kimura also cried on the last stage
This is Naho Tomisato.My name is Naho Tomisato.
This is Naho Tomisato.
I'd like to give you a quick quiz.
If you couldn't answer before me...
Please subscribe to our channel.
What is the name of my winning hamster?
Please subscribe to my channel because I won!
Bye-bye!